# SORO ISMAEI



ne



Loca tion

**FULL-STACK** Developer

in

skype



See more

Take a look at my LinkedIn profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ismael-soro-a1881185/



#### My website

### **PERSONAL INFORMATIONS**

I am an innovative fullstack developer with 3 years of experience in managing all aspects of the development process.

I love doing technology watch to know and learn every day. Used to working alone or in a team, I easily adapt to a SCRUM project team according to my responsibilities.

#### TRAINING

- 2017-2019 **MASTER IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING** Student at IFPG-ISFPT (ABIDJAN) with an average of 12.18 / 20
- 2008-2012 **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE** Student at Christ University (India) with an average of 63.50% over the 6 terms
- 2007 **GENERAL BACCALAUREATE** Serie: Mathematics and life and earth science

#### **EXPERIENCES**

APPLICATION ENGINEER: SNEDAI from 08/01/2017 to today

- Full-stack development of enrollment software for BROTO-IPP / CTSS.
- Development of SAMIA mission software.
- Development of modules for the transport license management application on behalf of the Directorate General of Taxes
- Development of Modules for e-purchase management software.

DEVELOPER: PETROCI from 02/13/2013 to 05/13/2013

Full-stack development of nursing management software

freeCodeCamp(<u>&</u>)



#### CERTIFICATIONS

FULL-STACK Developer with react.js and node.is

https://www.frecodecamp.org/certification/os mi2017/full-stack

CS50W web programming with JavaScript and python

https://certificates.cs50.io/0853a176-319d-4beb-8a99-

045a6fa57e72.pdf?size=letter

CS50x computer science with C and python https://certificates.cs50.io/f66c5560-4554-4c9d-bc11-4e1e4e4d72d9.pdf?size=letter

## LANGUAGE SK

HARVARD

React.js: 7.6 out of 10 F Node.js: 8.8 out of 10 ENGLISH: CURRENT

Python: 9.7 out of 10 Django: 9.7 out of 10 MVC: 9.7 out of 10